rameşaliyev

Senior Software Engineer

I'm a Software Developer mostly experienced in Web Technologies. I've worked in various companies as Lead and Senior Software Developer/Engineer. For the last couple of years, I returned to academia to improve my theoretical background.

experiences

Co-Founder & Full Stack Developer @ Ecma Co. Ltd.

Jun 2017 - Present

Senior Full Stack Developer @ Omma

Sep 2018 - Nov 2020 (2 year 3 months)

Senior Frontend Developer @ Pisano

Feb 2018 - Sep 2018 (8 months)

Lead Full Stack Developer @ Emlakjet

Jan 2016 - Oct 2017 (1 year 10 months)

Senior JavaScript Developer (Consultant) @ Turkcell

Oct 2013 - Dec 2015 (2 years 3 months)

JavaScript Developer @ E-NET Internet Technology Co.

Jan 2013 - Sep 2013 (9 months)

Frontend Developer @ Techpoint Labs

Mar 2012 - Jan 2013 (11 months)

Full Stack Developer @ Koridor Design Studio

Feb 2009 - Mar 2012 (3 years 2 months)

education

Yildiz Technical University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Engineering (2018 - 2022)

Sakarya University

Associate of Science - AS, Computer Programming (2016 - 2018)

Zeytinburnu Industrial Vocational High School

High School Diploma, Electronics (2004 - 2007)

volunteer experience

Instructor @ Frontend Camp'17 Summer Aug 2017

Organiser / Speaker @ JSNinjas - Free For All Aug 2015

Speaker @ The Frontiers:Mini Jun 2015

links

rames.dev
github.com/ramesaliyev
linkedin.com/in/ramesaliyev

contact

ramesaliyev@gmail.com